<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>callofcthulhu.straightjackets</packageId>
  <name>Call of Cthulhu - Straitjackets</name>
  <author>Jecrell</author>
  <url>https://discord.gg/AaVFA7V</url>
  <supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>
	<li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
	  <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
	  <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
	  <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
	  <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
	  <downloadUrl>https://patreon.com/jecrell</downloadUrl>
	</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>
		1.21.0.0 (06-01-2020)

		Straitjackets prevent colonists from hurting themselves and others by disabling mental breaks.

		Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

		These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me:
		Lumberjack, Shibby Says, TheJagermeister, Cory Bonifay, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Grendalloffen, Martin K. Bonde, Bentley Alsup, Eric Idema, MasterScootie, GoSu, Josh McCabe, spook, Clifford Campbell, J, CrankyPeanut, E_T, Finwej, Jonathan, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, John Kanady, Luis Figueroa, Midgeman, Nate Haug, Nemuri Hime, Richard Paul, SilentWeirdo, Calum, Calhoun Cattell, Keith Thoma, Tim Stillson, Dick Jones, Patrick, Nathan Getman, Populous25, Sharp Spook, Steven James, Marcus Sireanu, Mark, Emily Shaw, Drachken, Zalson, Baron Xot, Nicholas Bateman, Christopher, Justin Andres, Luis Salvatierra, TinyFloatingTurtle, George Chong Chuang Ming, John Boehr, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Robin Hager, Brachiaraidos, That Guy, Toc Anastar, Karol Rybak, Allic, Austin Harbert, Yewty, Evan Hwang, Ryan Brock, Jonathan Holzinger, MC, Alexander, Kevin Reagan, Alex Mederer, Toss Antilles, Chelsea Archambeau, Aron Glasser, Dan Winn, Fredric Sundberg, Sarah Banks, ted stevens

		========================
		Changelog
		========================
		1.21.0.0 (06-01-2020)
		========================
		Update for RimWorld 1.1.

		1.20.0.0 (10-19-2018)
		========================
		Initial release for RimWorld 1.0.

	</description>
</ModMetaData>